Up with People Archive 1937-2015 (bulk 1970-1990)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VII: Photographic material, 1960-2010
  - Subseries 2: Marketing, 1965-2010
    - Glossies, Super Bowl XX, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Glossies, Switzerland, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Glossies, Reed Thompson, undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Glossies, Time for the Music, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Glossies, Tucson Symphony, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Glossies, USSR, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Glossies, UWP Songwriter Hall of Fame Luncheon, 2010 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Glossies, various (1 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Glossies, various (2 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Glossies, various (3 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Glossies, various (4 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Glossies, various (5 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Glossies, various (6 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Glossies, various (7 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Glossies, various (8 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Glossies, various (9 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Glossies, various (10 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Glossies, various (11 of 11), undated (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Glossies, Viva la Gente, undated (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Glossies, Vive les Gens, undated (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Glossies, Washington D.C., undated (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Glossies, Cynthia Watson, undated (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Glossies, White House, Nixon, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Glossies, World in Motion, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - Glossies, Yugoslavia, undated (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - Merchandise, undated (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous (1 of 4), undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous (2 of 4), undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (3 of 4), undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous (4 of 4), undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Pace Publications (1 of 6), 1965-1969 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Pace Publications (2 of 6), 1965-1969 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Pace Publications (3 of 6), 1965-1969 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Pace Publications (4 of 6), 1965-1969 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Pace Publications (5 of 6), 1965-1969 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Pace Publications (6 of 6), 1965-1969 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Program layout, undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Promotional Shots, undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Promotional Shots, Bank of Boston, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Promotional Shots, Duplicates and Originals, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Scenery, Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Scheduling, Newspapers, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Scheduling, Slide Show, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Sing out, Korea, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Slide Presentation, 1970’s (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Souvenir Program transparencies, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Special effects and blank slides, undated (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Stand Together, Cast E, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Stand Together, TV commercial, Cast E (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Stand Together, TV commercial, Cast E (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - UWP Logo (1 of 2), undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - UWP Logo (2 of 2), undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - UWP Transparencies, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - UWP Website, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - World in Motion graphic concepts, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Yellow Jacket, with star mark, man, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Yellow Jacket, with star mark, woman, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: People, 1960-1998
    This series contains photographs, negatives and slides of various people connected to Up with People including casts. This series is arranged alphabetically by last name.
    - Cristie J. Aboussie, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Gardiner Ackley, US Ambassador to Italy, undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Miguel Aleman, Mexico, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - George Alexander, undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Muhammed Ali, Dick Gregory, undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Herb Allen, undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - John Allen, V.P. of “Readers Digest”, undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Desmond Anderson, Mayor of Edmonton, undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Mario Andretti, undated (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Vern Archer, “Toronto Star”, undated (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Marcussen Arco, undated (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Ken/Mary Ashby, undated (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Governor Askew, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Governor Apadoca, undated (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Governor Bruce Babbitt of Arizona, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Frank Bane, undated (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Nella Barkley, undated (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Gonzalo Barrios, Senator of Venezuela, undated (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - King Baudoin and Queen Fabiola, Belgium, 1969-1970 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Mrs. Beasley, undated (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Taylor G. Belcher, undated (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - J. Blanton Belk, 1970-1979 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - J. Blanton Belk, 1980-1984 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - J. Blanton Belk, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - J. Blanton Belk (1 of 3), undated (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - J. Blanton Belk (2 of 3), undated (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - J. Blanton Belk (3 of 3), undated (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Lt. Governor Bell-Irving, undated (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - Oren Benton, November, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - Donald P. Birdsale, undated (Box 50, Folder 38)
    - Herman Bliedbtreu, 1977-1981 (Box 50, Folder 39)
    - Lindon Blue, undated (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - Board (1 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 50, Folder 41)
    - Board (2 of 2), 1993-1995 (Box 50, Folder 42)
    - Yannick Boes, undated (Box 50, Folder 43)
    - Dr. Landrum R. Bolling, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 44)
    - Landrum Bolling, undated (Box 50, Folder 45)
    - Boston Public School, Headmaster and Headmistress, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 46)
    - Jim Boswell, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 47)
    - Henry Braun, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Pat Brogdon-Gomez, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Governor Otis Brown, Indiana, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Ambassador Walter Burns, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - President Bush, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Dick Capin, Advisory Board, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Prince Juan Carlos, Spain, 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Bill Carpenter, V.P. Public Affairs, Tenneco, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Francis Carry, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - President Carl Carstons, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - President Carstons, Germany, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Jimmy Carter, Ex-president of the USA, undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Cast A, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Cast A, 1969-1970 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Cast A, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Cast A, 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Cast A, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Cast A, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Cast A, 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Cast A, 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Cast A, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Cast A, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Cast A, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Cast A, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Cast A, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Cast A, 1985-1986 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Cast A, 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Cast A, 1990, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Cast A, 1997-1998 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Cast A, undated (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Cast A, B, C, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Cast A, B, C, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Cast A, B, C, D, E, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Cast A and Cast B, 1969-1970 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Cast A and Cast D, 1985-1986 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Cast A, B, C, D, contact sheets (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Cast A, B, C, D, contact sheets (2 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Cast A, B, C, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Cast A, B, C, D, E, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Cast A, European Cast, 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Cast B, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Cast B, 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Cast B, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Cast B (1 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Cast B (2 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Cast B (3 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Cast B (1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Cast B (2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Cast B (3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Cast B, 1976-1977 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Cast B, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Cast B, 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Cast B, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Cast B, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Cast B, 1982-1983 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Cast B, 1984-1985 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Cast B, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Cast B, 1987-1988 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Cast B, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Cast B, undated (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Cast B and C (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Cast B and C (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Cast C, 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Cast C, 1972- 1973 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Cast C, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Cast C, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Cast C (1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Cast C (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Cast C (1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Cast C (2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Cast C (3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Cast C, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Cast C, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Cast C, 1978-1979 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Cast C, 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Cast C, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Cast C, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Cast C, 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Cast C, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Cast C, 1982-1983 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Cast C, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Cast C, 1984-1985 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Cast C, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Cast C, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Cast C, 1991-1992 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Cast C, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Cast C, 1996-1997 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Cast C, January, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Cast C and Smithfields, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Cast C, undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Cast D, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Cast D, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Cast D, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Cast D, 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Cast D, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Untitled (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Cast D, 1982-1983 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Cast D, 1983-1984 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Cast D, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Cast D, 1984-1985 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Cast D, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Cast D, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Cast D, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Cast D, 1990-1999 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Cast D, undated (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Cast D and Cast E, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Cast D and Cast E, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Cast E, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Cast E, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Cast E, 1978-1979 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Cast E, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Cast E, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Cast E, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Cast E (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Cast E (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Cast E (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Cast E (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Cast E (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Cast E (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Cast E, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Cast E, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Cast E, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Cast E, European cast, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Casts, miscellaneous, 1970-1993 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Raul Castro, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Governor John Cavlin, Kansas, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Eugene Cernan, 1980-1982 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Cesar Chavez, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Vic Clough, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Bob Cochran, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - King Cole, undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Dorothy Collins, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Marcie Colpas, undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Colwell Brothers, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Paul Colwell, undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Ralph Colwell, undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Steve Colwell, undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - William Cone, undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Pete Conrad, undated (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Dana Cooper, undated (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Sister Kateri Cooper, Headmistress, undated (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Mary Crowley, President Home Interiors of Texas, undated (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Salvador Dali, 1971-1972 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Mrs. DeBacker, Belgium Minister of Culture, undated (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Senator DeConcini, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Commissioner DeGrazia, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Wesley M. Dixon, Jr., 1981 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - General Dozier, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Paul Duke, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Governor James Edwards, South Carolina, undated (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - J. Edwards, undated (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - General Dwight D. Eisenhower, undated (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Robert Ekler, undated (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Dr. Peter Ellis-Kellogg, 1982-1983 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Basil Entwistle, undated (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Chancellor Ludwig Erhardt, undated (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Bruce Erley, undated (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - European Cast, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Queen Fabiola, 1976-1979 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Frank Fields, undated (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Ambassador Firestone, US Ambassador to Belgium, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 42)
    - Pierre P Flimlin, undated (Box 54, Folder 43)
    - Ken Flower, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - Gerald Ford, Ex-president of the USA, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 45)
    - Dick Freeman, Board of Directors, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 46)
    - Rick Frisch, undated (Box 54, Folder 47)
    - Senator Fulbright, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 48)
    - John E. Fuller, undated (Box 54, Folder 49)
    - Dr. Felton Gamble, 1982-1983 (Box 54, Folder 50)
    - John Gardner, undated (Box 54, Folder 51)
    - German Parliament, undated (Box 54, Folder 52)
    - John Gonzalez, NBC Sports TV Director, Cast C, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 53)
    - Vernon Grigg, undated (Box 54, Folder 54)
    - Dale Gustafson, undated (Box 54, Folder 55)
    - Perh G. Gyllenhammar, President of Volvo-Sweden, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 56)
    - John Halward, 1982-1983 (Box 54, Folder 57)
    - Michael Hard, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 58)
    - P. Harnek, President Belgium Senate, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 59)
    - Lynn Hart, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 60)
    - Douglas Hartshorne, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 61)
    - Gloria Hemphill, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 62)
    - Ernest Henderson, undated (Box 54, Folder 63)
    - Luis Herrera, Ex-president of Venezuela, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 64)
    - Stefan Heymanns, undated (Box 54, Folder 65)
    - Dr. Hillary, President of the Republic of Ireland, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 66)
    - Jack Hipps, undated (Box 54, Folder 67)
    - Senator and Mrs. Holsclaw, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 68)
    - B.H. Honderick, President of Toronto Star, undated (Box 54, Folder 69)
    - Bob Hope, December 11, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 70)
    - Bob Hope, 1970-1971 (Box 54, Folder 71)
    - Host Families (1 of 2), undated (Box 54, Folder 72)
    - Host Families (2 of 2), undated (Box 54, Folder 73)
    - Hubert Humphrey, undated (Box 54, Folder 74)
    - Individual Portraits (1 of 3), undated (Box 54, Folder 75)
    - Individual Portraits (2 of 3), undated (Box 54, Folder 76)
    - Individual Portraits (3 of 3), undated (Box 54, Folder 77)
    - Individuals, staging, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 78)
    - Governor Bob James, Alabama, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 79)
    - Jerry Jarrett, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 80)
    - Paul Johnson, undated (Box 54, Folder 81)
    - Ken Johnson, undated (Box 54, Folder 82)
    - Mr. Jones, CEO General Electric, undated (Box 54, Folder 83)
    - Tuija Julie, undated (Box 54, Folder 84)
    - Preston Keevama, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 85)
    - Don Kendall, CEO Pepsico, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 86)
    - Myriam Keyson, undated (Box 54, Folder 87)
    - Governor Bruce King, New Mexico, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 88)
    - Kobler, undated (Box 54, Folder 89)
    - Arthur Koestler, undated (Box 54, Folder 90)
    - Alberto Kowarick, undated (Box 54, Folder 91)
    - Counselor Kozlowioz, Poland, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 92)
    - Chancellor Kriesky, Austria, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 93)
    - Chung II Kwon, Korean Premier, undated (Box 54, Folder 94)
    - Arnold Land, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Tom Landry, undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Prince Franz- Josef Lechtenstein, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Raul Leoni, President of Venezuela, undated (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - President Leone, 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - President Leone, Italy, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Marvin LeRoy, L.A. Benefit, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Jack Lewis, undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Liberace, Expo, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - John Lindsey, undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Princess of Lichtenstein, undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Lopez Portillo, Ex-president of Mexico, undated (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Los Angeles County Supervisors, undated (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Dave Mackay, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - James E. MacLennan, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Hubert Mandeville, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Bob Marbut, 1977-1978 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - William R. Mathew, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Matshushita Electric President, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Morris Martin, undated (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Russ Mawby, Kellog Foundation, undated (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Mayor of Barcelona, Spain, undated (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Mayor Kurtvijk, Belgium, undated (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Mayor of Little Rock, Arkansas, undated (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Mayor of New Orleans, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Mayor of Phoenix, undated (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Mayor of Salina, Kansas, undated (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Mayor of Selma, Alabama, undated (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Mayor of Washington D.C., undated (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Mayor York, Los Angeles, undated (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - David McCall Lovitt, undated (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Tom McCann, undated (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Tim McClearly, undated (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Bobbie McCloud, undated (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - McClusky, Indy 500, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Senator McCormick, Speaker of the House, undated (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - Tom McCurtin, Dallas Times/Herald, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 37)
    - McDermott, Air Force Academy, undated (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - James McDonald, undated (Box 55, Folder 39)
    - Jim McDonald, President of General Motors, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 40)
    - Governor John Mckeag, undated (Box 55, Folder 41)
    - Eric McTrelar, undated (Box 55, Folder 42)
    - Merrill Meigs, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 43)
    - James T. Morris, Lily Endowment, undated (Box 55, Folder 44)
    - Lynne Morris, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 45)
    - Vicki Monsour, undated (Box 55, Folder 46)
    - Matt Moutafis, undated (Box 55, Folder 47)
    - Yuichiro Muira, undated (Box 55, Folder 48)
    - Sayed Murad, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 49)
    - Kevin Murphy, President of Trailways, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 50)
    - Law Murphy, Mayor of Tucson, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 51)
    - Governor of Nebraska, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 52)
    - Dean Nelson, undated (Box 55, Folder 53)
    - Constance Berry Newman, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 54)
    - Richard Nixon, 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 55)
    - Non-U.S. cast contact sheets (1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 56)
    - Non-U.S. cast contact sheets (2 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 57)
    - Romulo O’Farrill, Sr. President of Novedades, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 58)
    - Oklahoma Senators, undated (Box 55, Folder 59)
    - R.B. “Buck” O’Reilly, undated (Box 55, Folder 60)
    - Jessie Owens, undated (Box 55, Folder 61)
    - Dan Pairlland, undated (Box 55, Folder 62)
    - John Parker, undated (Box 55, Folder 63)
    - Norman Vincent Peale, undated (Box 55, Folder 64)
    - S.K. Peatross, undated (Box 55, Folder 65)
    - Dale Penny, undated (Box 55, Folder 66)
    - President Pertini, Italy, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 67)
    - Fritz Philips, undated (Box 55, Folder 68)
    - Jim Plunkett, Oakland Raiders, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 69)
    - Sidney Poitie, undated (Box 55, Folder 70)
    - Pope John Paul II, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 71)
    - Pope John Paul II (1 of 4), undated (Box 55, Folder 72)
    - Pope John Paul II (2 of 4), undated (Box 55, Folder 73)
    - Pope John Paul II (3 of 4), undated (Box 55, Folder 74)
    - Pope John Paul II (4 of 4), undated (Box 55, Folder 75)
    - Pope Paul VI, undated (Box 55, Folder 76)
    - General Porter, undated (Box 55, Folder 77)
    - President of the Belgium Senate, undated (Box 55, Folder 78)
    - Anthony Quinn family, undated (Box 55, Folder 79)
    - Lady Ramsbotham, Bermuda, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 80)
    - Ramos Sanchez, undated (Box 55, Folder 81)
    - Prince Ranier and Princes Grace, Monaco, undated (Box 55, Folder 82)
    - Red Skelton, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 83)
    - Ember D. Reichgott, undated (Box 55, Folder 84)
    - Jack Revenscroft, undated (Box 55, Folder 85)
    - Wilson Riles, undated (Box 55, Folder 86)
    - Jose Antonio Rios Garcia, undated (Box 55, Folder 87)
    - John Roots, undated (Box 55, Folder 88)
    - Laura Rose, Director of Film Actor’s Workshop, undated (Box 55, Folder 89)
    - Ken Rossano, V.P., 1st National Bank of Boston, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Robert Royall, President of C & S banks, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Mrs. Pete Rozelle, 1981-1979 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Pek Rozelle, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Russian Astronaut, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Father Sobrino, Spain, undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Colonel Sanders, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Eisaku Sato, Prime Minister of Japan, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Don Saul, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Governor Shafer of Pennsylvania, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - John Schaeffer, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Bonnie and Larry Schaer, undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Hugo Scheltema, Dutch Ambassador, to U.N., undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Jack Scott, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Floyd W. Sedlmayr Jr., undated (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Lady Sharples, Bermuda, undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Jerald L. Shelsta, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Wally Shirra, undated (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Charles Shultz, Snoopy Creator, undated (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Show Creators, Allen, Morris, undated (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Show Creators, Allen, Murphy, Morris, undated (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Show Creators, Colwell, Murphy, undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Sargeant Shriver, undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Debbie Smith, undated (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Shelby Smith, Lt. Governor, Kansas, undated (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Roger Smith, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Smitherman, Attorney General, undated (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Lord Snowdon and Princess Margaret, undated (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Stahlman, Publisher Nashville Banner, undated (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - James Stewart, Japanese Liaison, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - John Steenhoven, undated (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - John R. Stills, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Carl B. Stokes, undated (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - Bob Story, undated (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Franz Josef Strauss, undated (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Barbara Streisand, undated (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Jan Sturges, undated (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Hugh Suest, undated (Box 56, Folder 38)